ohmojo.com 2019-05-11

# OhMojo.com Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to OhMojo.com is important to us. 

At OhMojo.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit OhMojo.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as your profile pictures and/or other preferences. 

We also use third party advertisements on OhMojo.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

**Collection of Personal Information from Site Visitors**   
OhMojo.com does not share any personal information supplied by you with other companies or organizations. Your information is only used in respect to your registration and/or membership with us. We do reserve the right to provide your information to the proper authorities if there has been misuse or questions regarding your membership (spam, harassment etc..) 

OhMojo.com uses cookies to customize web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends and the information may be used in the members section. OhMojo.com may place cookies on visitors hard drives to deliver information and content specific to your interests. Cookies are stored on the visitor's hard drive and are not stored, in any form, by OhMojo.com. 

**Use of Personal Data Collected**  
Your information is only used in respect to your registration and/or membership with us. We do not publish your personal information (such as email address, age, etc..) on your public profile without you explicitly making it public. Since your profile is published for other's to browse, the information listed on it is used for matching "search queries", and for you to better describe yourself and what you are looking for. OhMojo.com will not be liable for any information that you submit into the description sections of your public "personals" profile. 

**Opt-Out Right**  
Users can remove their registration information from our database by sending an email to mailbot@ohmojo.com. 

Email we send you is to facilitate your membership use. Email from us will always pertain to your account with us and/or to our website (e.g. to receive your password, to receive notices of messages waiting for you etc...). We occasionally send out emails to users based on their settings. Users can opt out of receiving this emails by changing their preferences in the "My Settings" section of the website. 

**Access to and Ability to Correct Personal Data**  
Upon request, OhMojo.com will provide a summary of any personal information retained by the us. OhMojo.com will only send personal records to the email address on file for the visitor name associated with it. Visitors may modify, correct, change or remove their personal records from the our database. 

**Collection of Personal Data From Children**  
The information and services at OhMojo.com, it's affiliates, sponsors and advertisers are not intended to be viewed by children under 18 years old. OhMojo.com will not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18 years of age. 

**OhMojo.com's Right to Contact User**  
OhMojo.com reserves the right to contact site visitors, regarding account status and changes to subscriber agreements, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to site visitors. 

**OhMojo.com's right to Change Privacy Policy**  
OhMojo.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. This policy will always be available on the website for review by visitors.
